export default  [
  {
    "category": "",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "Which one of these Microsoft subsidiaries doesn't noticeably use Java?",
    "correct_answer": "id Software",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Minecraft",
        "Yammer",
        "LinkedIn"
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "Behind .NET, what is the second most watched topic on Microsoft Docs?",
    "correct_answer": "Java",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Golang",
        "PHP",
        "NodeJS"
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "What was the codename for the Azure project, 15 years back?",
    "correct_answer": "Red Dog",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "MCS",
        "Copper",
        "Zune"
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "What is the license of Java binaries of the Microsoft Build of OpenJDK?",
    "correct_answer": "GPLv2",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Apache 2.0",
        "MIT",
        "Commercial License"
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "How many security experts does Microsoft employ dedicated to data security and privacy?",
    "correct_answer": "3,500",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "100",
        "1,500",
        "5,000"
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "What is a hashing function?",
    "correct_answer": "A hashing function is an algorithm that creates a fixed-length hexadecimal value of the plaintext.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "A hashing function is an algorithm that creates a new ciphertext message from the plaintext.",
        "A hashing function is an algorithm that's used to decrypt ciphertext from the sender.",
        "A hashing function is an algorithm that creates a new key pair."
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "What is the latest model Azure OpenAI model announced (GA) at build?",
    "correct_answer": "GPT-4o",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "GPT-4Vision",
        "GPT-4Turbo",
        "GPT-4Whisper"
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "GitHub",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "What is InnerSource?",
    "correct_answer": "Bringing Open Source Practices to our internal development (e.g. removing silos)",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "An early phase of Open Source Adoption",
        "When code is locked down to the teams that need it",
        "A program used to build an Open Source community internally (e.g. drive usage adoption in a secure way, encourage contributions, recognition for OSS work among employees, etc.)"
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "GitHub",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "What is GitHub Copilot Workspace?",
    "correct_answer": "A Copilot-native developer environment",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "A space where you can build copilots",
        "The next version of GitHub Copilot",
        "An addition to GitHub Codespaces"
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "GitHub",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "What is an NPU?",
    "correct_answer": "Neural Processing Unit",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Network Processing Unit",
        "NLP Processing Unit",
        "Negative Processing Unit"
      ]
  }
]